If what you want to get in
the immediate
And what you plan to get in
the future
The immediate collection
When nasi'a, the one you want
to
collect later
If they are the same
No problem
You want to get 10,000 naira
today
Two weeks time you get the
10,000
They are the same,
no problem
In that case you can argue
that
What you get immediately is
better than
what you get later
So if what you are saying is
that
You will get 10,000 naira now
And hereafter on the day of
Qiyamah
When you abstain from sin
It is that same 10,000 naira
of
this dunya that Allah will
give you
Then your statement may be
correct
So if what you want to
collect
in the immediate
And what you will collect in
the
future
If they are the same
You can say what you are
saying
It is better to collect it
immediately
But if they are different
If in the immediate
You would collect 10,000
naira for example
And in one year's time of the
same transaction
You will collect one million
You will collect one billion
He said
Then collecting it later is
better and
much more
It is better
And more advantageous
So if your argument to be
correct
That you want this dunya,
dunya, dunya